KEIICHI KATSUNO

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

/ COFFEE ENTHUSIAST



PROFILE

A Frontend Developer, originally from Japan. Passionate about business improvement with "Kaizen" that has a real influence on people's lives.

My career progression has zigzagged for the past 7 years, from Sales & Marketing / Clients Relationship Development in trading in Japan, Production Quality Management in third-waved coffee in the UK and Colombia, and now I am involved in Web Development in Melbourne, Australia, trying to invent a websolution to overcome the industrial issues I have faced in my past experiences.

Those journey has always been shaping my personality and growing my confidence to survive in this real competitive world. Now, I deeply understand what I want to do / should do / will do in my life.

I place a high value on Integrity, having Respect to people and diverse cultures, and Proactivity and Responsibility in making my own decision.

EXPERIENCE

- AUSTRALIA

Frontend Web Developer - Freelance

June 2020 - Present

- as a Freelance. Melbourne
 - Web Site Development on Ruby on Rails
 - UI/UX Design

Coffee Production Assistant - Part-Time

October 2020 - Present [Coffee Roastery]

- at Small Batch Roasting Co., Melbourne

• Production Roasting & Management for The Local Market

- COLOMBIA

Coffee Production Inspector - Internship

Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

- at InverCafé Ltda, Chinchiná

[Coffee Farm/Exporter]

- Production Quality Control & Assessment of Specialty Coffee
- Deep Industrial Knowledge

- THE UK

Coffee Production Manager - Full-Time

- at The Roasting Shed Co, London

July 2018 - Sep 2019 [Coffee Roastery]

- Production Roasting & Management of High-Quality Coffee
- Local Market Research & Analysis of Needs-Meeting for Clients

- JAPAN

Clients Relationship Manager - Full-Time

Apr 2013 - July 2017 [Trading Company - Shosha]

- at Yuasa Trading Co, Tokyo

- Relationship Development with stakeholders, while ensuring successful sales, marketing and negotiation in the Japanese hardware manufacturing.
- Day to day Account & Order Management for my personal clients in the fastpaced trade environment

EDUCATION

Software Development - Computer Science

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

- at Le Wagon, Melbourne, Australia
 - Web Development in Rails and Javascript
 - UX/UI Design

Q Arabica Coffee Grader Training

Feb 2020 - Feb 2020

- at Japan Coffee Exchange, Shizuoka, Japan
 - General Knowledge of Coffee Production
 - Presice Coffee Production Assessment

Bachelor of Business Administration

Apr 2009 - Mar 2013

- at KinDai University, Osaka, Japan

Outside of study, I engaged in an American Football club where I learned:

- My own way of the Leadership & Team Management
- Logical Thinking for Organisational Success as well as Individual Success

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Problem solving by Logical Thinking
- Clients Relationship Development
- Web Development in Ruby
 - UX/UI Design

Paal Ringstad

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Weight Training, Meditation and Yoga
- American Football
- Non-Fiction (History, Anthropology, Biology, Nutrition, Psychology etc)
- Food & Beverage Industry (Third-Waved Coffee, Craft Beer and Wine)
- Information Technology (Software Development, BigData, AI, IoT etc)

REFFERENCES

Michael Allen

Operator of Small Batch Roasting Co. 040 146 8528

Operator of Le Wagon Melbourne 042 396 7255



